export const QuizDatas= [
    {
        question: "Which language runs in a web browser?",
        option1:"Java",
        option2: "C", 
        option3:"Python",
        option4: "JavaScript",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What does CSS stand for?",
        option1: "Central Style Sheets", 
        option2: "Cascading Style Sheets", 
        option3: "Cascading Simple Sheets", 
        option4: "Cars SUVs Sailboats",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        option1:  "Hypertext Markup Language",
        option2:  "Hypertext Markdown Language", 
        option3:  "Hyperloop Machine Language", 
        option4:  "Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What year was JavaScript launched?",
        option1:  "1996",
        option2:  "1995", 
        option3:  "1994", 
        option4:  "none of the above",
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        option1: "Virtual Dom",
        option2: "Original Dom",
        option3: "Both A and B",
        option4: "None of the above",
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is ReactJS?",
        option1: "Server-side framework",
        option2: "User-interface framework",
        option3: "Both A and B",
        option4: "None of the above",
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question: "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside",
        option1: "Render with arguments",
        option2: "SetState",
        option3: "PropTypes",
        option4: "Props",
        answer:4,
    },
    {
        question: "Who created React.js?",
        option1: "Jordan Mike",
        option2: "Jordan Walke",
        option3: "Time Lee",
        option4: "Jordan Lee",
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Babel?",
        option1: "JavaScript Compiler",
        option2: "JavaScript Inerpreter",
        option3: "JavaScript Transpiler",
        option4: "None of the above",
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question: "Identify the command used to create a react app.",
        option1: "npm install create-react-app",
        option2: "npm install -g create-react-app",
        option3: "install -g create-react-app",
        option4: "None of the above",
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
        option1: "3000",
        option2: "3306",
        option3: "3030",
        option4: "8080",
        answer:4,
    },
    {
        question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
        option1: "1",
        option2: "2",
        option3: "3",
        option4: "4",
        answer:1,
    },
    {
        question: "What are arbitrary inputs of components in react also known as?",
        option1: "Elements",
        option2: "Props",
        option3: "Keys",
        option4: "Ref",
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question: "Among The following options, choose the one which helps react for keeping their data uni-directional?",
        option1: "Dom",
        option2: "Flux",
        option3: "Jsx",
        option4: "Props",
        answer:2,
    },
    {
        question: "Using which of the following command can prevent default behaviour at in react?",
        option1: "PreventDefault()",
        option2: "avoidDefault()",
        option3: "revokeDefault()",
        option4: "None of the above",
        answer:1,
    },
   
];